[indistinct chatter]
- YOU'VE BEEN DOING THIS NOW
FOR--HOW MANY YEARS IS IT?
- TWO YEARS.
HOW MUCH LONGER
DO YOU GIVE YOURSELF
DOING THIS THING, GOING AROUND
BEING A SORT OF A--
- I...I DON'T KNOW.
I NEVER THOUGHT
I'D BE DOING IT
FOR TWO YEARS EVEN,
YOU KNOW.
[Moves Like Jagger
intro playing]
♪ ♪
- ♪ OH, AH ♪
♪ OH ♪
♪ JUST SHOOT FOR THE STARS
IF IT FEELS RIGHT ♪
♪ THEN AIM FOR MY HEART
IF YOU FEEL LIKE ♪
♪ AND TAKE ME AWAY,
AND MAKE IT OKAY ♪
♪ I'LL SWEAR I'LL BEHAVE ♪
♪ YOU WANTED CONTROL,
SO WE WAITED ♪
♪ I PUT ON A SHOW,
NOW I MAKE IT ♪
♪ YOU SAY I'M A KID,
MY EGO IS BIG ♪
♪ I DON'T GIVE A [...] ♪
♪ AND IT GOES LIKE THIS ♪
♪ TAKE ME BY THE TONGUE
AND I'LL KNOW YOU ♪
♪ KISS ME TILL YOU'RE DRUNK
AND I'LL SHOW YOU ♪
♪ ALL THE MOVES LIKE JAGGER ♪
♪ I'VE GOT THEM MOVES
LIKE JAGGER ♪
♪ I'VE GOT
THE MOVES LIKE JAGGER ♪
♪ I DON'T NEED TO TRY
TO CONTROL YOU ♪
♪ LOOK INTO MY EYES
AND I'LL OWN YOU ♪
♪ WITH THEM MOVES
LIKE JAGGER ♪
♪ I'VE GOT
THE MOVES LIKE JAGGER ♪
♪ I'VE GOT THE MOVES
LIKE JAGGER ♪
♪ MAYBE IT'S HARD ♪
♪ WHEN YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE BROKEN AND SCARRED ♪
♪ NOTHING FEELS RIGHT ♪
♪ BUT WHEN YOU'RE WITH ME,
I'LL MAKE YOU BELIEVE ♪
♪ THAT I'VE GOT THE KEY ♪
♪ OH, SO GET IN THE CAR ♪
♪ WE CAN RIDE IT
WHEREVER YOU WANT ♪
♪ GET INSIDE IT,
AND YOU WANT TO STEER ♪
♪ BUT I'M SHIFTING GEARS,
I'LL TAKE IT FROM HERE ♪
♪ OH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ AND IT GOES LIKE THIS ♪
♪ TAKE ME BY THE TONGUE
AND I'LL KNOW YOU ♪
♪ KISS ME TILL YOU'RE DRUNK
AND I'LL SHOW YOU ♪
♪ ALL THE MOVES LIKE JAGGER ♪
♪ I'VE GOT THEM MOVES
LIKE JAGGER ♪
♪ I'VE GOT
THE MOVES LIKE JAGGER ♪
♪ WHOO ♪
♪ I DON'T NEED TO TRY
TO CONTROL YOU ♪
♪ LOOK INTO MY EYES
AND I'LL OWN YOU ♪
♪ WITH THEM MOVES
LIKE JAGGER ♪
♪ I'VE GOT
THE MOVES LIKE JAGGER ♪
♪ I'VE GOT THE MOVES
LIKE JAGGER ♪
- ♪ UNH, YOU WANNA KNOW
HOW TO MAKE ME SMILE ♪
♪ TAKE CONTROL,
OWN ME JUST FOR THE NIGHT ♪
♪ BUT IF I SHARE MY SECRET ♪
♪ YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
KEEP IT ♪
♪ NOBODY ELSE CAN SEE THIS ♪
♪ UNH, SO WATCH AND LEARN ♪
♪ I WON'T SHOW YOU TWICE ♪
♪ HEAD TO TOE,
OOH, BABY, RUB ME RIGHT ♪
♪ BUT IF I SHARE MY SECRET ♪
♪ YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
KEEP IT ♪
♪ NOBODY ELSE CAN SEE THIS,
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- ♪ AND IT GOES LIKE THIS ♪
♪ TAKE ME BY THE TONGUE
AND I'LL KNOW YOU ♪
- ♪ TAKE ME BY THE TONGUE ♪
- ♪ KISS ME TILL YOU'RE DRUNK
AND I'LL SHOW YOU ♪
♪ ALL THE MOVES LIKE JAGGER ♪
♪ I'VE GOT THEM MOVES
LIKE JAGGER ♪
♪ I'VE GOT
THE MOVES LIKE JAGGER ♪
- ♪ OH, YEAH ♪
- ♪ I DON'T NEED TO TRY
TO CONTROL YOU ♪
♪ LOOK INTO MY EYES
AND I'LL OWN YOU ♪
♪ WITH THEM MOVES
LIKE JAGGER ♪
♪ I'VE GOT
THE MOVES LIKE JAGGER ♪
♪ I'VE GOT THE MOVES
LIKE JAGGER ♪
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
- I THINK WE'RE
SORT OF PRETTY WELL SET UP
FOR AT LEAST ANOTHER YEAR.
- [giggling]